#### Contact

marmstrong669@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/michelle-armstrong-59193b120 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Healthcare

Healthcare Management

Certifications
CMSRN

# Michelle Armstrong

Clinical Nurse Manager-Endoscopy at UC Health Cincinnati, Ohio Area

### Summary

Experienced Nursing Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Management, Endoscopy, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS). Strong healthcare services professional with a Masters in Nursing Administration degree from Indiana Wesleyan University.

## Experience

UC Health Clinical RN Manager-Endoscopy January 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months) Cincinnati, Ohio

TriHealth
Nurse Manager II
March 2018 - January 2019 (11 months)
Cincinnati Area, KY

TriHealth Endoscopy Center North Assistant Nurse Manager Endoscopy November 2013 - March 2018 (4 years 5 months) Cincinnati, Ohio

The Christ Hospital Health Network Registered Nurse January 2012 - February 2013 (1 year 2 months) Cincinnati, Ohio

Endoscopy

Atrium Medical Center Staff Registered Nurse June 2011 - January 2012 (8 months) Middletown, Ohio Endoscopy Center North Staff Registered Nurse June 2008 - June 2011 (3 years 1 month) Cincinnati, Ohio

TriHealth
Staff Registered Nurse
December 2007 - June 2008 (7 months)
Cincinnati, Ohio

BERNSTEIN ALLERGY GROUP, INC. Registered Nurse June 2007 - December 2007 (7 months) Cincinnati, Ohio

The Christ Hospital Health Network Staff Registered Nurse August 2005 - June 2007 (1 year 11 months) Cincinnati, Ohio

#### Education

Medical Surgical

Indiana Wesleyan University

Master's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2016 - 2018)

Indiana Wesleyan University
Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2016)